I'd sit alone and watch your light
My only friend through teenage nights
Everything I had to know
I heard it on my radio
You gave them all those all time stars
Through wars of worlds, invaded by Mars
You made'em laugh, You made'em cry
You made us feel like we could fly
So don't become some background noise
A backdrop for the girls and boys
Who just don't know or just don't care
And just complain when you're not there
You had your time, you had the power
You've yet to have your finest hour
Radio
Everybody
All we hear is radio ga ga
Radio goo-goo, radio ga-ga
All we hear is radio ga-ga
Radio blah blahh
Radio, what's new?
Radio, someone still loves you
We watch the shows, we watch the stars
On videos for hours and hours
We hardlly need to use our ears
How music changes through the years
Let's hope you never leave, old friend
Like all good things, on you, we depend
So stick around 'cause we might miss you
When we grow tired of all this visual
You had your time, you had the power
You've yet to have your finest hour
Radio
All we hear is radio ga-ga
Radio goo-goo, radio ga-ga
Radio blah blah
Radio, what's new?
Radio,
someone still loves you
Loves
you